A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14 FA286
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 3
  - Provo, Utah - Monthly Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 92, Folder 1222)
  - Provo, Utah - Monthly Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 92, Folder 1223)
  - Provo, Utah - Monthly Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 92, Folder 1224)
  - Provo, Utah - Monthly Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 92, Folder 1225)
  - Provo, Utah - Monthly Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 92, Folder 1226)
  - Provo, Utah - Monthly Reports, 1939-1947 (Box 92, Folder 1227)
  - Provo, Utah - Monthly Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 93, Folder 1228)
  - Provo, Utah - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1948 (Box 93, Folder 1229)
  - Provo, Utah - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1948 (Box 93, Folder 1230)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1231)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1232)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1233)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1234)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1235)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1236)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1237)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1238)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1939-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1239)
  - Provo, Utah - Prepayment Plan - Forms and Contracts, 1940-1942 (Box 93, Folder 1240)
  - Provo, Utah - Public Health Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1946 (Box 93, Folder 1241)
  - Provo, Utah - Publicity - Brochures and Clippings, 1939-1956 (Box 93, Folder 1242)
  - Provo, Utah - Site Selection Data, 1937-1939 (Box 94, Folder 1243)
  - Provo, Utah - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1939-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1244)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Audit Report, 1946-1948 (Box 94, Folder 1245)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, 1942-1946 (Box 94, Folder 1246)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Building Requisitions (Box 94, Folder 1247)
    Change Orders - September 17, 1946-January 14, 1949 Pre-Qualification Statements - OCtober 2-8, 1945
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1946-1949 (Box 94, Folder 1248)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1946-1949 (Box 94, Folder 1249)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1946-1949 (Box 94, Folder 1250)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1946-1949 (Box 94, Folder 1251)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1946-1949 (Box 94, Folder 1252)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Building Requisitions - Equipment Data, 1945-1946 (Box 94, Folder 1253)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1947-1948 (Box 94, Folder 1254)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 1255)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Equipment - Work Sheets, 1945-1948 (Box 95, Folder 1256)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Fellowships (C-U), 1942-1952 (Box 95, Folder 1257)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Field Trip Memoranda, 1942-1951 (Box 95, Folder 1258)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1942 (Box 95, Folder 1259)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1942 (Box 95, Folder 1260)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1942 (Box 95, Folder 1261)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1942 (Box 95, Folder 1262)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1942 (Box 95, Folder 1263)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1942 (Box 95, Folder 1264)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1942 (Box 95, Folder 1265)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1266)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1267)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1268)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1269)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1270)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1271)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1272)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1273)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1274)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1275)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1276)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1942-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1277)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1278)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1279)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1280)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1281)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1282)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1942-1951 (Box 97, Folder 1283)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Medical Education Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1950 (Box 97, Folder 1284)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 97, Folder 1285)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 97, Folder 1286)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 97, Folder 1287)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 97, Folder 1288)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 98, Folder 1289)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 98, Folder 1290)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 98, Folder 1291)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 98, Folder 1292)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 98, Folder 1293)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports, 1951-1953 (Box 98, Folder 1294)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Monthly Reports - Financial, 1946-1949 (Box 98, Folder 1295)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Nurse Education Program - Correspondence and Memoranda, June-September, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 1296)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1949-1950 (Box 98, Folder 1297)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, April 24, 1942 (Box 98, Folder 1298)
  - Sikeston, Missouri - Site Selection Data, 1938-1943 (Box 98, Folder 1299)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Audit Reports, 1936-1937, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 1300)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, June-September, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 1301)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Building Requisitions (Box 99, Folder 1302)
    Change Orders - November 20, 1936-August 16, 1937 Purchase Orders (Extra Building) - September 22, 1937-July 8, 1940
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1936-1950 (Box 99, Folder 1303)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1936-1950 (Box 99, Folder 1304)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1936-1950 (Box 99, Folder 1305)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1936-1950 (Box 99, Folder 1306)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1936-1950 (Box 99, Folder 1307)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Building Requisitions - Pre-Qualification Statements, May-June, 1936 (Box 99, Folder 1308)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Disbursements, 1937-1942 (Box 99, Folder 1309)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1937-1941 (Box 99, Folder 1310)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1937-1941 (Box 99, Folder 1311)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1937-1941 (Box 99, Folder 1312)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1936-1938 (Box 100, Folder 1313)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1936-1938 (Box 100, Folder 1314)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Fellowships (B-Z), 1937-1941 (Box 100, Folder 1315)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Field Trip Memoranda, 1935-1946 (Box 100, Folder 1316)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Field Trip Memoranda, 1935-1946 (Box 100, Folder 1317)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Field Trip Memoranda, 1935-1946 (Box 100, Folder 1318)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1937 (Box 100, Folder 1319)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1937 (Box 100, Folder 1320)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1937 (Box 100, Folder 1321)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1926-1937 (Box 100, Folder 1322)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1323)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1324)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1325)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1326)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1327)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1328)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1329)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1330)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1331)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1332)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 1333)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1950-1958 (Box 102, Folder 1334)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1926-1950 (Box 102, Folder 1335)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Minutes - Executive Committee and Membership Meetings, 1935-1936 (Box 102, Folder 1336)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1935-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1337)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1935-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1338)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1935-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1339)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1935-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1340)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1935-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1341)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1935-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1342)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1935-1945 (Box 102, Folder 1343)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1945-1949; 1951 (Box 103, Folder 1344)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1945-1949; 1951 (Box 103, Folder 1345)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1945-1949; 1951 (Box 103, Folder 1346)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1945-1949; 1951 (Box 103, Folder 1347)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1945-1949; 1951 (Box 103, Folder 1348)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1945-1949; 1951 (Box 103, Folder 1349)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Monthly Reports, 1945-1949; 1951 (Box 103, Folder 1350)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1935-1947 (Box 103, Folder 1351)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Accounting Procedures, May-June, 1939; May 1941 (Box 103, Folder 1352)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Accounting Procedures, May-June, 1939; May 1941 (Box 103, Folder 1353)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Agreement (Mississippi Hospital and Medical Service and Member Hospitals), September 1947 (Box 103, Folder 1354)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1355)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1356)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1357)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1358)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1359)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1360)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1361)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1362)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1937-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1363)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1937-1949 (Box 104, Folder 1364)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Forms and Contracts, 1939-1948 (Box 104, Folder 1365)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Reports, 1939-1942; 1944; 1948; 1951 (Box 104, Folder 1366)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Reports, 1939-1942; 1944; 1948; 1951 (Box 104, Folder 1367)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Prepayment Plan - Reports, 1939-1942; 1944; 1948; 1951 (Box 104, Folder 1368)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Public Health Plan - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1938-1941 (Box 105, Folder 1369)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Publicity - Annual Reports to the Community, 1956-1957 (Box 105, Folder 1370)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Site Selection Data, 1935-1936 (Box 105, Folder 1371)
  - Tupelo, Mississippi - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1937-1947 (Box 105, Folder 1372)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Accounting Manual Instruction - Correspondence and Memoranda (Box 105, Folder 1373)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Audit Reports, 1928-1930, 1932-1933, 1948-1950 (Box 105, Folder 1374)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Audit Reports, 1928-1930, 1932-1933, 1948-1950 (Box 105, Folder 1375)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Contracts, November-December, 1928 (Box 105, Folder 1376)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1933; 1942-1944 (Box 105, Folder 1377)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1933; 1942-1944 (Box 105, Folder 1378)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1933; 1942-1944 (Box 105, Folder 1379)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1933; 1942-1944 (Box 105, Folder 1380)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1933; 1942-1944 (Box 105, Folder 1381)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Building Requisitions (Box 105, Folder 1382)
    Credit Orders - November 16, 1928-September 15, 1930 Extra Orders - March 25, 1929-September 12, 1930
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Disbursements, 1929-1932 (Box 105, Folder 1383)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Disbursements, 1933-1942 (Box 106, Folder 1384)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1928-1933 (Box 106, Folder 1385)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1928-1933 (Box 106, Folder 1386)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Equipment - Work Sheets, 1929 (Box 106, Folder 1387)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Fellowships (B-J), 1929-1946 (Box 106, Folder 1388)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Fellowships (L-N), 1929-1946 (Box 106, Folder 1389)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Fellowships (P-W), 1929-1946 (Box 106, Folder 1390)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1935 (Box 106, Folder 1391)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1935 (Box 106, Folder 1392)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1935 (Box 106, Folder 1393)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1935 (Box 106, Folder 1394)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Field Trip Memoranda, 1936-1946 (Box 107, Folder 1395)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Field Trip Memoranda, 1936-1946 (Box 107, Folder 1396)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1397)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1398)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1399)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1400)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1401)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1402)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1403)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1404)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1945 (Box 107, Folder 1405)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1966 (Box 108, Folder 1406)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1966 (Box 108, Folder 1407)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1966 (Box 108, Folder 1408)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Hospital Proper - Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1927-1950 (Box 108, Folder 1409)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Minutes - Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1930-1944 (Box 108, Folder 1410)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1930-1943 (Box 108, Folder 1411)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1930-1943 (Box 108, Folder 1412)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1930-1943 (Box 108, Folder 1413)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1930-1943 (Box 108, Folder 1414)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1930-1943 (Box 108, Folder 1415)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1944-1949 (Box 109, Folder 1416)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1944-1949 (Box 109, Folder 1417)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1944-1949 (Box 109, Folder 1418)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1944-1949 (Box 109, Folder 1419)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Monthly Reports, 1944-1949 (Box 109, Folder 1420)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1940 (Box 109, Folder 1421)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1940 (Box 109, Folder 1422)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence, Memoranda, Forms and Contracts, 1940-1942 (Box 109, Folder 1423)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Public Health Program - Financial Correspondence, 1929-1932 (Box 109, Folder 1424)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Public Health Program - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1927-1932 (Box 109, Folder 1425)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Publicity - Hospital Brochures, 1945-1955 (Box 109, Folder 1426)
  - Wauseon, Ohio - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1930-1948 (Box 109, Folder 1427)
- Rochester Regional Plan, 4
  - Annual Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 110, Folder 1428)
  - Annual Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 110, Folder 1429)
  - Annual Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 110, Folder 1430)
  - Audit Reports, 1946-1951 (Box 110, Folder 1431)
  - Budgets, 1946-1954 (Box 110, Folder 1432)
  - Budgets, 1946-1954 (Box 110, Folder 1433)
  - Budgets, 1946-1954 (Box 110, Folder 1434)
  - By-Laws - Administrators Conference, Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals Inc. and Medical Conference, May-June, 1946 (Box 110, Folder 1435)
  - Capital Projects - Albion (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1948-1951 (Box 110, Folder 1436)
  - Capital Projects - Albion (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1948-1951 (Box 110, Folder 1437)
  - Capital Projects - Bath (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1950 (Box 110, Folder 1438)
  - Capital Projects - Brockport (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1949 (Box 110, Folder 1439)
  - Capital Projects - Canadaigua (Bonds and Contracts), 1950-1951 (Box 110, Folder 1440)
  - Capital Projects - Canadaigua (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1948-1955 (Box 111, Folder 1441)
  - Capital Projects - Canadaigua (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1948-1955 (Box 111, Folder 1442)
  - Capital Projects - Canadaigua (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1948-1955 (Box 111, Folder 1443)
  - Capital Projects - Canadaigua (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1948-1955 (Box 111, Folder 1444)
  - Capital Projects - Corning (Bids, Bonds, Change Orders and Contracts), January 1949 and December 1950 (Box 111, Folder 1445)
  - Capital Projects - Corning (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1951 (Box 111, Folder 1446)
  - Capital Projects - Corning (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1951 (Box 111, Folder 1447)
  - Capital Projects - Corning (Equipment Work Sheets), 1949 (Box 111, Folder 1448)
  - Capital Projects - Cuba (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1938-1949 (Box 111, Folder 1449)
  - Capital Projects - Dansville (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1951 (Box 111, Folder 1450)
  - Capital Projects - Dansville (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1951 (Box 111, Folder 1451)
  - Capital Projects - Dansville (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1951 (Box 111, Folder 1452)
  - Capital Projects - Geneva (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1946-1949 (Box 111, Folder 1453)
  - Capital Projects - Geneva (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), January-May, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 1454)
  - Capital Projects - Hornell (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1950 (Box 112, Folder 1455)
  - Capital Projects - Hornell (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1950 (Box 112, Folder 1456)
  - Capital Projects - Montour Falls (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1948-1950 (Box 112, Folder 1457)
  - Capital Projects - Penn Yan (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1458)
  - Capital Projects - Penn Yan (Correspondence, Reports and Memoranda), 1947-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1459)
  - Capital Projects - Field Trip Memoranda, 1945-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1460)
  - Capital Projects - Field Trip Memoranda, 1945-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1461)
  - Capital Projects - Field Trip Memoranda, 1945-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1462)
  - Capital Projects - Field Trip Memoranda, 1945-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1463)
  - Capital Projects - Field Trip Memoranda, 1945-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1464)
  - Capital Projects - Field Trip Memoranda, 1945-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1465)
  - Capital Projects - Field Trip Memoranda, 1945-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1466)
  - Five-Year Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH) Plan of Action (1951-1955), November 1948 (Box 113, Folder 1467)
  - Five-Year Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH) Report (1946-1950), December 1954 (Box 113, Folder 1468)
  - Five-Year Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH) Report (1946-1950) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1953-1954 (Box 113, Folder 1469)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1470)